Track 3.8 Unit 3 Lesson 6 Activity 2
Bài 3.8 Bài 3 Tiết 6 Hoạt động 2
Listen and follow the routes
Nghe và đi theo các tuyến đường
Which park were they at?
Họ ở công viên nào?
Yesterday Aunt Daisy was at the supermarket
Hôm qua Dì Daisy ở siêu thị
Then she was at the bookshop
Rồi dì ở hiệu sách
Then she was at the train station
Rồi dì ở ga tàu
Then she was at the hospital
Rồi dì ở bệnh viện
Then she was at the bank
Rồi dì ở ngân hàng
And then she was at the park next to the bank
Và rồi dì ở công viên cạnh ngân hàng
Which park was Aunt Daisy at?
Dì Daisy ở công viên nào?
Yesterday Ella and Flo were with our grandparents
Hôm qua Ella và Flo đi với ông bà
First they were at the bus stop
Đầu tiên họ ở trạm xe buýt
Then they were at the zoo
Rồi họ ở sở thú
After that they were at the library
Sau đó họ ở thư viện
Next they were at the swimming pool
Tiếp theo họ ở bể bơi
Then they were at the shopping centre
Rồi họ ở trung tâm mua sắm
And after that they were at the park next to the shopping centre
Và sau đó họ ở công viên cạnh trung tâm mua sắm
Which park were Ella and Flo at?
Ella và Flo ở công viên nào?
Yesterday I was very busy
Hôm qua mình rất bận
In the morning I was at the supermarket
Buổi sáng mình ở siêu thị
Then I was at the bookshop
Rồi mình ở hiệu sách
In the afternoon I was at the cafe with my cousins
Buổi chiều mình ở quán cà phê với các anh chị em họ
Then I was at the library looking for a book
Rồi mình ở thư viện tìm sách
After that I was at the zoo with my friends
Sau đó mình ở sở thú với bạn bè
Next to the zoo there's a park
Cạnh sở thú có một công viên
And after the zoo we were in that park
Và sau khi đi sở thú chúng mình ở công viên đó
Which park was I at?
Mình ở công viên nào?
Yesterday Ella and Flo were at the park next to the bookshop
Hôm qua Ella và Flo ở công viên cạnh hiệu sách
Next to the library
Cạnh thư viện
Then I was at the library
Rồi mình ở thư viện
In the morning I was at the library
Buổi sáng mình ở thư viện
And after the library I was at the bookshop
Và sau khi đi thư viện mình ở hiệu sách
In the morning I was at the library
Buổi sáng mình ở thư viện
And after the library I was at the bookshop
Và sau khi đi thư viện mình ở hiệu sách